<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Life | Tech Pool]]></title>
  <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/categories/life/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-11-12T11:32:00+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://mengzhiqc.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[KavinDream]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[lenye01@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[AngelHack Day]]></title>
    <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/11/12/angelhack-day/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-12T10:25:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/11/12/angelhack-day</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<pre>
    http://snacks.dreambuff.com
    The Entrance Of Your Mobile Web App. Here Your Go!
</pre>


<h4>Two Wonderful Days</h4>

<p>Last Satuday, I join a hackthon in IKC with my friends wov. Why I attend this activity? Maybe lacking practice of program makes me feel unset.</p>

<p>We met another friend, a graduate from DongNan Univercity, a very nice boy.  we plan to start a project based on HTML5. This project provide an entrance of Web App. As we all know, web app become more and more popular in china , Almost all componies begin to pay more attentions to it, that&rsquo;s great!</p>

<h4>Division of labor</h4>

<p>I used to write backend services before, so zjh and I were in charge of writing backend program. wov is good at frontend program, that&rsquo;s his job. the backend program&rsquo;s main language is nodejs, A javascript framework base on commonjs. OK, we were programing as this &hellip;</p>

<h4>Episode before end</h4>

<p>There will be half an hour before the end. After merging an code writen by wov, the picture can&rsquo;t present correctly . that&rsquo;s not an good news, we must fix this bug. fortunately, we fix this bug at last.</p>

<h4>Write at the end</h4>

<p>This activity is very meaningful, we met a new friend. we can complete a project in two days. if our passing is existed, the sky will be always blue.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Response For A Long Time]]></title>
    <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/09/15/no-response-for-a-long-time/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-15T19:53:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/09/15/no-response-for-a-long-time</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Have a long time not to update my blog, Something confusing me, I have not enough passion to exploer new floor.</p>

<p>I should slow my pace and think about that happens to me. What is my dream? What is my target? What should i be tomorrow? Life is tough, how can i face it.</p>

<p>Interesting things. And what?</p>

<p>Find more interesting things, Think more and not just run, when your passion is exhausted, what you can?</p>

<p>Keep reading. Every book has its special meanings for you!</p>

<p>Come on! encourage myself!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Campaign For Manager]]></title>
    <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/08/14/campaign-for-manager/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-14T21:05:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/08/14/campaign-for-manager</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I join campaign for iOS Developer Manager this afternoon. Actually this is my second time stand at this stage, feeling little nervers. about 9 other managers review my campaign speech, they ask some questions about my management in iOS department this half of year.
Thanks for this chance, if i was elected finally, i will do my best to become a excellent manager.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Career! Am I A Developer?]]></title>
    <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/08/07/new-career-am-i-a-developer/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-07T21:08:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/08/07/new-career-am-i-a-developer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today is Wednesday, A teamleader of my team come back, he have planed to leave team in 2 weeks, at last he decide to stay here, I&rsquo;m glad to hear that this morning and he is the first person who turns his heart in my manage career.</p>

<p>I know I am not a developer at the moment, I&rsquo;m a manager, if my leader give me a work, I can do it well, more than they expect, that&rsquo;s good feel.</p>

<p>Choice between &ldquo;do things right&rdquo; and &ldquo;do right thing&rdquo;, maybe i needn&rsquo;t to choose, they can both exist, doing things right is the base ability of a manager, more than this, we should do right thing and lead the team to the right direction.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hot Day, Passion Release]]></title>
    <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/08/01/hot-day-passion-release/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-01T08:50:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/08/01/hot-day-passion-release</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The temperature is above 35 centidegrees for about a week, Many people have no energy to do what they should do, No passion, feel exhausting&hellip;</p>

<p>I&rsquo;ll not do like this. Release my Passion, in this hot day. Too many excited things i wanna face .</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
