<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Category: Life | Tech Pool]]></title>
  <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/categories/life/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-09-15T20:01:40+08:00</updated>
  <id>http://mengzhiqc.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[KavinDream]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[lenye01@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[No Response For A Long Time]]></title>
    <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/09/15/no-response-for-a-long-time/"/>
    <updated>2013-09-15T19:53:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/09/15/no-response-for-a-long-time</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Have a long time not to update my blog, Something confusing me, I have not enough passion to exploer new floor.</p>

<p>I should slow my pace and think about that happens to me. What is my dream? What is my target? What should i be tomorrow? Life is tough, how can i face it.</p>

<p>Interesting things. And what?</p>

<p>Find more interesting things, Think more and not just run, when your passion is exhausted, what you can?</p>

<p>Keep reading. Every book has its special meanings for you!</p>

<p>Come on! encourage myself!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Campaign For Manager]]></title>
    <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/08/14/campaign-for-manager/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-14T21:05:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/08/14/campaign-for-manager</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I join campaign for iOS Developer Manager this afternoon. Actually this is my second time stand at this stage, feeling little nervers. about 9 other managers review my campaign speech, they ask some questions about my management in iOS department this half of year.
Thanks for this chance, if i was elected finally, i will do my best to become a excellent manager.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Career! Am I A Developer?]]></title>
    <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/08/07/new-career-am-i-a-developer/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-07T21:08:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/08/07/new-career-am-i-a-developer</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Today is Wednesday, A teamleader of my team come back, he have planed to leave team in 2 weeks, at last he decide to stay here, I&rsquo;m glad to hear that this morning and he is the first person who turns his heart in my manage career.</p>

<p>I know I am not a developer at the moment, I&rsquo;m a manager, if my leader give me a work, I can do it well, more than they expect, that&rsquo;s good feel.</p>

<p>Choice between &ldquo;do things right&rdquo; and &ldquo;do right thing&rdquo;, maybe i needn&rsquo;t to choose, they can both exist, doing things right is the base ability of a manager, more than this, we should do right thing and lead the team to the right direction.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hot Day, Passion Release]]></title>
    <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/08/01/hot-day-passion-release/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-01T08:50:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/08/01/hot-day-passion-release</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The temperature is above 35 centidegrees for about a week, Many people have no energy to do what they should do, No passion, feel exhausting&hellip;</p>

<p>I&rsquo;ll not do like this. Release my Passion, in this hot day. Too many excited things i wanna face .</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Persuasion]]></title>
    <link href="http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/07/31/data-persuasion/"/>
    <updated>2013-07-31T13:59:00+08:00</updated>
    <id>http://mengzhiqc.github.io/blog/2013/07/31/data-persuasion</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We always make decision everyday, some are correct, and some are wrong. It is strange that when we encount a result that benefit for us, we think it is right , even though lacking evidences. why?</p>

<p>Yestoday i describe a issue that i make wrong decision. If I respect the data from BI department, I will find the trick earlier. so, from now on, according to data, not just deciding with feeling.</p>

<p>Improving our &ldquo;Data Persuasion&rdquo;, it is import!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
